thermoworks.com 2019-10-20

# Terms & Conditions

**ThermoWorks appreciates the trust you place in us and we are committed to protecting the privacy of the personal information you make available to us. If ever you have a question or concern about the information we collect or how we use it, please do not hesitate to contact us at 1-800-393-6434 or 801-756-7705 or  [info@ThermoWorks.com](mailto:%20info@thermoworks.com). **

 **What information does ThermoWorks collect?**  
We may collect information from you (including name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, and other transactional information) when you...

  * Place an order from our website
  * Place an order from one of our catalogs
  * Subscribe to one of our email lists
  * Request a catalog
  * Create an account at www.ThermoWorks.com
  * Submit a product for service or repair
  * Enter a contest or sweepstakes
  * Inquire about our services

We maintain the data that you share with us in a secure database along with a record of your purchases. 

We also gather information about how visitors to www.ThermoWorks.com navigate their way through our website (including IP addresses and the broad demographic data associated with them).

How does ThermoWorks use the information it collects?

We only use information we collect from you for as long as it is reasonably required for a legitimate business purpose. We are legally required to hold some types of information to fulfill our statutory obligations, such as for tax records, or to confirm your warranty. We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as necessary for the relevant activity. We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information to:

  * Process and track your orders
  * Process repairs, calibrations and other services you request
  * Contact you about the status of an order or service request
  * Send you product and promotional information at your request
  * Tailor our product selection, inventory and online services to better suit your needs

Does the ThermoWorks website use "cookies"?

Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer by a website. ThermoWorks.com does use cookies to...

  * Remember what items are in your shopping cart
  * Recognize you when you return to our website
  * Remember information you enter into forms on the website

If you have cookies (or javascript) disabled on your computer, you may not be able to complete an order in our shopping cart. Please place your order by calling 1-800-393-6434 or 801-756-7705.  
We also use web beacons (also known as tracking pixels) and other analytics/tracking technologies to advertise to you online. Site visitors can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en).

How does ThermoWorks use email?

Those who subscribe to one of our email lists can expect to receive email offers detailing exclusive price offers, close-outs, new-product announcements and other information about ThermoWorks and thermometry in general. You may opt out of receiving emails from ThermoWorks at any time, either by clicking the "unsubscribe" link provided at the bottom of every email or by accessing your account preferences by logging in at www.ThermoWorks.com.

Does ThermoWorks share email addresses or other information with any third parties?

No, ThermoWorks does not rent, sell, loan or share our email list or any other information that we gather to any third party.

Children Under The Age of 16

ThermoWorks.com is not intended for children under 16 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16 or knowingly allow such persons to create a ThermoWorks.com account. If you are under 16, please do not use or provide any information on ThermoWorks.com. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us using phone numbers or email address specified in the header paragraph of this document and we will delete the information. 

How Can I Opt Out of Marketing Communications?

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive direct marketing from us you can click “unsubscribe” in the emails you receive and it will automatically remove you from our email subscriber database.   
Opting out of our first-party advertising-related cookies or out of third-party advertising-related cookies and web beacons does not necessarily mean that you will not see our advertising—only that this advertising will not be targeted to you through the use of first-party or third-party cookies, web beacons or related technologies. 

How does ThermoWorks protect your information?

ThermoWorks maintains its data in a secure, password-protected database and employs encryption and other security technologies to protect the transfer of credit card numbers and other personal information. Feel free to contact us for more information about security technologies employed by ThermoWorks.  
We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. To guard your information delivered to us electronically, our web sites use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). SSL encrypts your credit card number, name and address so only we are able to decode your information. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your contact information, to the extent permitted by law, we do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our web sites, and you do so at your own risk.  
We urge you to keep any password that you establish with us in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also remember to log off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place. 

What about other websites that ThermoWorks links to?

From time to time, ThermoWorks provides links to other websites as a service or convenience to our customers. Sites that are not owned by ThermoWorks are not governed by this privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy and security policies of any website that you visit.

Are the policies subject to change?

Yes, ThermoWorks reserves the right to change these policies from time to time in order to better serve you but any such changes will always be reflected here.
